Guide to the Stanford University, School of Humanities and Sciences, Innovative Academic Courses, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-1992-086
  - Terry Bright (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - SWOPSI Intramural Baseball Roster, Spring 1976 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - John Martin's SWOPSI Paper 1976 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Merlyn- Staff, pay, info. etc. (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Katchadourian Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Student Co-Director Applications Spring 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Staff 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - NISS Reports 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - SWOPSI Sponsorship of Achrites 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - SWOPSI Public Events and Editorial Policy (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - SWOPSI Search for Professional Co-Director 1977 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Student Co-Director Search 1977 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - SWOPSI Search Administration 1977 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Hoover Outreach 1977 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - BAKKE Symposium October 17, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Spring Tuesday Community Politics in the 1970's (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - IRA Sandperl: Program on Ireland 1977 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Public Interest Law Foundation (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Dickenson Symposium (N.P.) 1977 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Dickinson 1977 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Handbook Original 1977 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Revised Handbook Draft 1977 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - SWOPSI Handbook for Workshop Leaders 8/77 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - SUPTON Chapter 1977 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Supton Chapter Original 1977 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Arms Control (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Mechanization and Farm Workers (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Native Americans (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Nuclear Power (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Puerto Rican Conference (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - South Africa (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Women's Week (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Student Co-Director Search 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - SWOPSI Student Co-Director Chris Coleman 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - SWOPSI Budget 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - CUS/ SWOPSI Charge Memos 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - SWOPSI General 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Enrollment Figures, Fall 1974-1978 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Public Events: Policies (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - SWOPSI Public Events: Background and Finances (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - The Learning Exchange (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Instructors Orientation Fall 1978, Winter 1979 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - SWOPSI Community Workshop Leaders 1974-1978 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Senate Charge: Responses to Queries 2/22/78 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Senate Report Charge 1978 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Controversy Related to SWOPSI 155 Invasion of Privacy (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Regsitrar's Office Crse. File, Study Lists, Green Petitions, Graduation, End Quarter Reports, Room Scheduling (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Shockley- SWOPSI Case (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - SWOPSI Clarification of the Action Component (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Original Draft of Report to CUS (Change Renewal) March 1978 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Handbook Original Summer 1978 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Revision of SWOPSI Handbook 1978 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board Letters 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Old Catalogues (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - SWOPSI Student Co-Director Lisa Foster 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Advisors' Orientation: 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Publicity (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Department Credit (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - NISS Report on SWOPSI (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Public Events: 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Dorm Representatives: 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Outreach Contact People: 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Outreach: Alumni 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Summary Statistics (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - S. Coalition on Health Care Issues (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - The EDP's Joint Project (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Office Manual Originals (Box 42, Folder 60)
  - Letters to Instructors: 1978-1979, 1979-1980, 1980-1981 (Box 42, Folder 61)
  - Rape Education (Box 42, Folder 62)
  - Sponsor / Leader Interview Notes 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - NISS 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - SWOPSI General 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Solar Car (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Public Events (folder mixed up) (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Alumni Association (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Journalism and Hoover Possibilities with SWOPSI (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Corporate Responsibility (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Academic Information Center (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Highlander School (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Instructors Bag Lunches 1977-1980 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Policy Board Letters 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - SWOPSI Student Co-Director 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Student Co-Director Search 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Student Co-Director Application Search 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - SWOPSI Student Co-Director Cruz-Elena Sandquist 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Co-Director, memos, ads, etc. 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Public Events 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Medical Students Assoc. (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Health Care Coalition, Meeting with Kennedy 1978-1980 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Teaching 1979 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Public Events 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Public Events Record 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - SWOPSI Logo Contest 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Workshop for Student Organizations 1970-1980 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - S.F. Mime Troupe 1979 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - RA's Contact List: 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Program Assistant- Job Search Materials- Originals, Fall 1980 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Course Development 1980 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Ruth's Stats/ Enrollment Stats 1980 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Workshops for Instructors (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Teaching Services 1980 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - SWOPSI Photos for Catalog (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Publicity: Information and Ideas (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - SWOPSI Grading Records: Summary (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - "War at Home" Oct. 1980 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Women's Issues (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Sara Evans, April 8, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Policy Board 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board Information, 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Policy Board Mailings 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Central America (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Public Events 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - SWOPSI Public Events 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - SWOPSI Student Co-Director's Search for 1979-1981 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - Student Co-Director Search 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - Budget Meeting with Herant 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - SWOPSI Staff Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - Planning 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - Black Perspectives in Law- Speakers (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - SWOPSI Professional Co-Director Search 1981 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Student Co-Director Search Spring 1981 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Co-Director Search Summer 1981 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Untitled (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Background for 1981 C-US Report and Charge (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Abbreviated C-US Report 3/81 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - NISS Report/ C-US Report/ Charge 1981 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Original File Copy plus Carbon of C-US Report 2/81 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - SWOPSI Course Review 1981 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Public Service History of EDPs (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Teaching Aids for EDP Instructors (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - SWOPSI Public Events Fall 1975 to Spring 1981 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Possible SWOPSI Special Events (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Rape Education Week 10/81 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - OSOC Materials (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Workshops for SWOPSI Students (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Draft- Procedures Manual SWOPSI (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Draft- Instructor's Handbook (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - LABOR Studies File (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Military Conversion Information (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Dell' Arte Players (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Policy Board 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Policy Board Information 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Policy Board Mailings 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Student Co-Direcotor Search 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - SWOPSI Staff Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Public Events 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Group Process/ Student Participation Resources and Worksheets (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Workshop for Workshop Leaders "Questions" Fall Quarter 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Workshop for Workshop Leaders- Winter Quarter 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Spring Instructor Workshop 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Guest Professorship/ Information/ GPD (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Information: Access for Physically Limited 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Computer Typesetting Information (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Daily Ads/ Business 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Instructions for Instructors 1980-1982 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Administrative Review of Odus 1982 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Building Progressive Student.... February 1982 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (Misc) 1982 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - SWOPSI Academic/ Industrial Relations (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Entreprenuership (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Staff Workshops (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Resourse File- Public Events (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Disorientation Week April 6 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Disorientation Week Schedules (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Disorientation Week Programs and Speakers Information (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Events and Services, facilities for Disorientation Week (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Disorientation Week Newsprint Informarion Schedule (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Disorientation Week Publicity Information (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Disorientation Week Funding Proposals and Information, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Disorientation Reciepts (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Art in Action April 1982 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Political Theatre (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Original C-US Report of 11/1/83 (1981-1982 + 1982-1983) (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - SWOPSI Student Co-Director Applications for 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - SWOPSI Staff Meetings 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Fall Quarter Instructor Workshop- "Guest Speakers" 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Winter Quarter Instructor Workshop- "Questions" 1982-1982 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Instructions to Instructors 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Daily Ads/ Business 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Action Projects By Type 1981-1983 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Socialism 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - George Moffat (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Student Co-Director Search 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - C-US Report to AD HOC Committee, Novemeber 1983 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Personnel Humanities and Sciences Meetings with Sydney (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Spring Quarter Catalogue, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Instructor Bag Lunch Spring 1983 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Preparation- Funding Workshop for Social Change Parameters- May 1983 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Workshop: Funding for Social Change (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Major's Fair- May 10, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Political Theatre Workshop 11/12/83 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Faculty Publication Planning 1983 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Film File Information Brochures (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Resource File: Course Development (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Resource Articles, A-L (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Resource Articles, M-Z (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Misc. Course Articles (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Black Issues (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - Fem Studies (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Women's Music Concerts (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Holliman, Elaine L (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - Handbook for Workshop Leaders (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Original Handbook Rewrite 12/83 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - C-US Information/ Chronology 1983-1985 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Policy Board 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Co-Director Seach 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Student Co-Director Search for 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - SWOPSI Co-Director Applications, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Proposal Information On Funing (Grant Information) 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - SWOPSI Staff Meetings 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Public Events Funding- Cover Sheets (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Staff Meetings 1983-1985 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Personnel Forms Summer 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Fall Quarter Catalogue, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Winter quarter Catalogue 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Fall Quarter SWOPSI Poster 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Winter Quarter Poster 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Spring Quarter Poster 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Public Events 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Public Events Reference Forms (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - SWOPSI Public Events Forms (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Instructor Workshop "Developing Course Objectives" Fall Quarter 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Instructor Workshop "Guest Speakerrs" Fall Quarter 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Non-credit Self-Defence Workshops, Fall 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - SWOP 198 Section 1 and 2 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Information for 1984 C-US Report (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Arrow Report 1984 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Response to Ad. HOC Report Oct. 25, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - AD HOC Report on EDP's 1984 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Response to AD HOC Review Report October, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - OA III Job Search Confidential (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Student Co-Director (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Publication (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Restructuring SWOPSI To IAC (Winkler Files) (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Student Response to Reorganization (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Support Letters to SWOPSI (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - SWOPSI Stationary (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Handbook Revision Business (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Public Events: The Animal Film (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Scire Community Service Faire, 4/84 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Community Service Fair/Flyer 4/84 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Thank You Party, June 4, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Humanists (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Nicaragua (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - Elderly Concerns (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - Health Issues (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - Danilo Dolci (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - SWOPSI Public Events, "On Guard" Fall, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - Hanrahan, Noel (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - Burnett, Andre S. (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - Jurin-Reid, Barbara (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Hours Worked (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - 1984 (Box 46, Folder 50)
  - Publications Fund Info. and Correspondence Circa 1972 (Box 46, Folder 51)
  - Final Edited Handbook Text 1/84 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Course Proposal Papers (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Policy Board 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Student Co-Director Search, 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - SWOPSI Staff Meetings, 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Public Events 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Public Events Proposals 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Public Events Statistics 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Instructor Workshop and Action Projects, Fall 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Action Projects Lists By Year (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Program Descriptions- IAC 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Course Development 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Fall Quarter Catalogue, 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Winter Quarter Catalogue Poster 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Spring Quarter Catalogue, 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Mailing List for SWOPSI Catalogs (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Fall Quarter Poster 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Winter Quarter Poster 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Spring Quarter Poster, 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Poster on Student Involvement in SWOPSI Spring 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - IAC Logo Contest-Spring 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - IAC Flyer (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Type Set Word/Phrases (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - SWOPSI From Outside Stanford, 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - 610 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Meetings with Associate Dean (Lougee) (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Paying Instructors (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Publicity Lists 1985 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Work/Study Student's Tasks (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Innovative Academic Courses (IAC) (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Workshop Forms Revisions for IAC 1985 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Catalogue Letterhead IAC 1985 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - SWOPSI Reception, May 1985 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Non-Violence 1985 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Sexual Harrassment (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Jelliffe, Elizabeth H. (Betsy) (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Atha, Kerry (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Kerry Atha, Personnel (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Delores Huff- Stanford (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Meetings with Associate Dean Lougee 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - UPSE Information (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Student Director Search 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Faculty/ Staff Contact List (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Library Privlages for IAC Insructors, 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - IAC Staff Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - Graduate Studies Office Memorandum on the Tuition Grants 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - Fall: Workshop for IAC Instructors 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - Completed IAC Instructor Agreement (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - Course Review- Notes and Meetings 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - Class Enrollments Fall 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - Statistics: Number of Course Offerings (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - Statistics: Workshops Offering Grades (Box 47, Folder 52)
  - Statistics: Sponsors By Categories (Box 47, Folder 53)
  - Statistics: Categories of Workshops (Box 47, Folder 54)
  - Statistics: Instructors by Categories (Box 47, Folder 55)
  - Statistics: Number of Students By Year (Box 47, Folder 56)
  - Statistics: Students By Majors (Box 47, Folder 57)
  - Publicity Information/ Promotion (Box 47, Folder 58)
  - Student Groups Constitutions (Box 47, Folder 59)
  - Temporary Employees- time Sheets Etc. 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 60)
  - Time Schedule Input/ Corrections, 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 61)
  - Mailings to IAC Board 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 62)
  - IAC Potential Board Members, 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 63)
  - IAC Catalogue Fall 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 64)
  - Winter Quarter Catalogue 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 65)
  - IAC Catalogue Winter 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 66)
  - Spring Quarter 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 67)
  - Poster Fall Quarter 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 68)
  - IAC Poster Winter Quarter 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 69)
  - IAC Pamphlet 1985-1986 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Public Events Proposals, Fall Quarter 1985-1986 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Public Events Proposals, Winter Quarter 1985-1986 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Public Events Proposals Spring Quarter 1985-1986 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Action Projects 1985-1986 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Critical Legal Studies (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Statistics: Total Enrollment (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Course Evaluation Reports Spring 1986 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Enrollment Data 1986 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Mini-Course Proposals Winter 1986 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Academic Council Member List (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Work Study (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - SWOPSI Form Letters (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - California Tomorrow (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Sample Press Releases/ PSAS/ Posters (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - SWOPSI Publicity By Workshop Leaders (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - FSS Ideas Winter 1986 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - IAC Policy Statement (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - IAC Staff Job Descriptions (Winkler File) (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Public Events Slix Dobkin (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Jack Winkler - Personnel file (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Summer School 1985-1986 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - SWOPSI Policy Board Description Applications, 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Student Co-Director Search 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Undergraduate Director Search 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Accreditation Committee 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Accreditation Committee 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - IAC Accreditation Committee (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Information on Registration Precedures from the Registrar's Office 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Catalog Copy, 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - FSS Replies for 1986/1987 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Procedures (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Public Events Planning 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Public Events 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Public Events Funding, 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Western Culture 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Courses 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - Instructions Workshop Handout and Presentation Materials 1/12/87 (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - Christic Institute (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - SWOPSI Proposals Winter 1987 (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - Peace Mobile Proposal: Jean Islabaslic (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - Issue: Reagan Library (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - Affirmative Action (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - SE Asian Refugees (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - Social Movements of the 60's (Box 48, Folder 45)
  - Street Theatre Workshop, 1/31/87 (Box 48, Folder 46)
  - Resident Fellows Fall 1987-1988 (Box 48, Folder 47)
  - Proposals, Fall 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 48)
  - Course Proposal Info. Desk Copies (Box 48, Folder 49)
  - Student Movement and Education Coll and Hernandez (Box 48, Folder 50)
  - Public Events: Manual/ Appendix (Box 48, Folder 51)
  - Accreditation Committee Notes 1988-1989 (Box 48, Folder 52)
  - Accreditation Committee Evaluation for Spring 1989 (Box 48, Folder 53)
  - Press and Documentary (Box 48, Folder 54)
  - SWOPSI Reunion, 10/89 (Box 48, Folder 55)
  - Solomonow: Nonviolence ATSC (Box 48, Folder 56)
  - Margo Hom: Remarks at SWOPSI 20th Reunion October 11, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Public Interest Science in the Controversy SWOPSI (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Accreditation Fall 1990 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Accreditation Committee Evaluations for Winter 1990 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - IAC Accreditation Spring 1990 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - SWOPSI Reports Historical Docs. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - SWOPSI Proposals (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Eastern Europe (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Environment (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Food Issues (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Housing and Homelessness (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - New World Legacy (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Sustainable Agriculture- Richard Strong (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Accreditation Tally, Comments Fall 1991 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Accreditation: Winter 1991 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Grant Proposals, October 1991 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Budget and Expenses Statments (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - IAC Program Review: Jones Committee June 14, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Comm. Tally Spring1991 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Misc. Notes (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - "Indigenous" Course (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Horn: In Coming IAC Correspondence 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Horn: IAC Out Going Correspondence 9/1990-6/1992 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Accreditation, Winter 1992 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Accreditation Voter: Spring 1992 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Sonia Johnson SWOPSI Guest Professor January 1992 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Public Event: "Rosie the Riveter" (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - SWOPSI Stationary and Letterhead Graphic (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Handbook Xeroxes (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Stanford Maps (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Stanford Maps (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Stanford Publication Services (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Library Information (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Address Lists (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Meeting Scheduler (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Collaborative Learning (Supplement to Handbook) (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - OATQ Forms (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Student Employment Forms (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Flyers Ads for IAC Events (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Alternative Press/ Kay (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Walton/ Out In Suburbia (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Don Kennedy (Box 49, Folder 42)